Guide to the PricewaterhouseCoopers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Coopers & Lybrand Series II: Printed materials
  - Subseries II.3: Periodicals
    - Compendium of Published Materials, 1973 - 1992 (Box 28, Folder 9 - 10)
    - Computer Assurance Services (CAS) Notes, 1995 - 1997 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Coopers Journal, Nos. 18 - 21, 27, 1969 - 1977 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - C&L Journal, Nos. 30 - 35, 37, 39, 1978 - 1982 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Core of the Apple, New York, NY, 1982 - 1990 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - The Critical Edge, 1994 - 1995 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Developments Affecting Financial Reporting, Nos. 12 - 24, 1982 - 1995 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Developments Affecting Governmental Financial Reporting, Nos. 1 - 2, 1989 - 1991 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Executive Briefing, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Focus on C&L Consulting, 1994 - 1997 (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Footnotes, Los Angeles Office, CA, Jun. 1975 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Growing Your Business, 1993 - 1997 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Growing Your Wealth Newsletter, Summer 1995 (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Health Legislation Washington Newsletter / Washington Outlook, 1986 - 1987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Human Resources Advisory, Vols. I - V, 1993 - 1997 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - In the Know, 1993 - 1994 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - International Services Division Newsletter, 1961 - 1962 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Investment Company Perspectives, 1994 -1996 (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Knowledgeline, 1995 - 1996 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Knowledgelink, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Lybrand Tax Newsletter, Jun. 1959 - Aug. 1961 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Management Services Newsletter, 1960 - 1962 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Our Firm, Nov. 1982 - Dec. 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - People & Lybrand, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Prognosis (Health care reform watch), 1994 - 1995 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Profile, 1973 - 1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - The Q, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - The Quantum Leap, 1996 - 1997 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Review, 1996 - 1997 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Time-Line, 1968 - 1980 (Box 29, Folder 11 - 12)
    - Your Firm, 1977 - Jul 1982 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      [Continued as Our Firm]
  - Subseries II.4: External Publications
    External Printed matter containing materials related to C&L or articles about C&L
    - The Accountants Digest, Vo. 1 - 2, Sep. 1935 - Jun. 1937 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Arthur Andersen & Co. Addresses by Leonard Spacek, 1956 -1757 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - American Institute of Accountants Bulletins, Vol. 1, 1916 - 1924 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - American Institute of Certified Public Accountants AICPA publications, 1952 - 1977 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - AT&T Annual Reports, 1920, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - AT&T USA vs. AT&T, Dec. 1982 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - The Corporate Accountant, UK, Jul. 1933 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Incorporated Accountants Journal, Aug. 1933 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Journal of Accountancy, 1987 - 1997 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - National Association of Cost Accountants Official Publications, Dec. 1919 - Aug. 1921 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Pace University The Pace Student, 1923 - 1925 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Putnam Management Company Putnam Equities Fund Annual Report, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Steel Industry materials, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous external printed materials, 1953 - 1997 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - The Auditors Have Arrived- Fortune Magazine Article, 1960, 2 (Water Damage) (Box 346, Folder 6)
    - Columbia University Montgomery Library of Accountancy, 1927 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Coopers & Lybrand Series III: Photographs
  All transparencies are done in color, although some of them depict early b&w photographs
  - Subseries III.1: Centennial Book Illustration Photos
    - Sub-subseries III.1.1: Numbered Illustrations
      Illustrations identified by number. For image description see photolist
      - Polaroids: Ad-001, Awd-001 -- Awd-003; Awd-008 -- Awd-010; Chm-001 -- Chm-013; Pht-077; Pht-080; Prs-002; Partners' Meeting at Seaview Country Club, 1954; Partners' Wives at Partners' Meeting, 1955; unidentified dinner; [C&L in China]; Montgomery's Auditing; N.E. Auerbach; Defliese, Auerbach, Jennings and Staub., 38 (polaroids) (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Transparencies: Book Cover, Awd-001; Awd-004 -- Awd-005; [C&L Cup -Awd-007]; Awd-008 -- Awd-010; Bk-003 -- Bk-005; Bk-015 -- Bk-033; Bk-050; Bk-051., 29 (2.5 x 3 color transparencies), 12 (4 x 5 color transparencies) (Box 30, Folder 2)
        [Book cover - 4 images, 2 copies each]
      - Transparencies: Chm-001 -- Chm-013; Ch3-041, Inv-001 -- Inv-003, 14 (2.5 x 3 color transparencies), 4 (4 x 5 color transparencies) (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Prints and cards: Ad-005; Awd-006; Bk-023; Chm-001; Chm-002; Chm-004; Inv-006; Inv-007; Log-010; Log-011; 1920 - 1973, 3 (8 x 10 b&w print), 1 (2 copies) (5 x 7 b&w print), 3 (card), 5 x 7 color prints) (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Pht Prints: Pht-001 -- Pht-015, 15 (8 x 10 b&w print) (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Pht Prints: Pht-017; Pht-018; Pht-020; Pht-021; Pht-026 -- Pht-028; Pht-037; Pht-044; Pht-048 -- Pht-051, 10 (8 x 10 b&w print), 1 (5x7 color print), 5 (5x7 b&w print) (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Pht Prints: Pht-066 -- Pht-076; Pht-084; Pht-086 -- Pht-091; Pht-096 -- Pht-100, 5 (8 x 10 b&w print), 2 (5x7 color print), 4 (5x7 b&w print), 3 x 5 b&w print), 1 (8 x 10 color print), 3 (4 x 6 color prints) (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Pht Series Negatives and Transparencies: Pht-001 -- Pht-018; Pht-020; Pht-021; Pht-031; Pht-033; Pht-037; Pht-036; Pht-040; Pht-042, Pht-043; Pht-052; Pht-053; Pht-061; Pht-077 -- Pht-081; Pht-99A; Pht-101, 23 (4 x 5 b&w negatives), 17 (2.5 x 3 color transparencies), 1 (4 x 5 color transparency) (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Transparencies: Prs-001; Prs-002; Pst-001; Sld-001 --- Sld-023, 3 (2.5 x 3 color transparencies), 23 (4 x 5 color transparencies) (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Sld Series: Copy Slides Sld-001 - Sld-023, digital printouts. (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Drew University; University of Pennsylvania Audit courses: Pht-042; Pht-043, identifications enclosed, Philadelphia, 1966, 2 (b&w digital print) (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Multiple copies of Slides: [Group of executives at lounge with flowers]; Bk-048; Pht-095; Scr-006, 39 (35 mm color slides), 2 (35 mm b&w slides) (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Sub-subseries III.1.2: Unnumbered historical images
      - Centennial Book Cover Designs, 6 (8 1/2 x 11 color Transparencies - Framed) (Box 347, Folder 1)
      - Lybrand, William; Ross, Edward; Ross, Adam; Montgomery, Robert. LRB&M Company founders negatives, 4 (4 x 5 b&w negatives), 1 (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Lybrand, William; Ross, Edward; Montgomery, Robert. LRB&M Company founders prints, 2 (8 x 10 b&w print), 1 (5 x 7 b&w print (mounted)), 1 (3 x 5 b&w print) (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - LRB&M Our first office, Philadelphia, PA, 1 (3 x 4 b&w print (mounted)), 2 (b&w digital print) (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Coolidge, Calvin; Edison, Thomas A.; Heins, John; Vail, Theodore N. AT&T Photos from LRB&M Journal, 2 (3 x 4 b&w print (mounted)), 1 (4 x 5 b&w print (mounted)), 1 (2 x 3 b&w print (mounted)) (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Deloitte, William Deloitte & Touche Portrait photo, 1845, 1 (6 x 8.5 color print) (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - LRB&M Cuba Cane Sugar Account - scrapbook page, [1926-1927], 2 (3 x 4 b&w print (mounted)) (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - LRB&M Buildings and interiors: American Cities expansion pictures - Book Building and Ford HQ in Detroit, MI; Parker Honnifin in Cleveland, OH. Puck Buildings, [1934 - 1990s], 6 (8 x 10 b&w print), 1 (8 x 10 color print), 1 (5 x 7 color print) (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Defliese, Philip; Auerbach, Norman; Jennings, Alvin; Staub, Walter; Moscarello, Louis; Crosby, Ralph; LRB&M; Coopers Bros Historical Group photos. Name Identifications on some., 3 (5x7 b&w print), 4 (8 x 10 b&w print), 2 (8 x 10 color print), 4 x 5 color print) (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - LRB&M Company Meetings - Oversized. Name indexes enclosed., Seaview Country Club, [NY], 1951 - 1955, 8 (b&w prints) (Box 347, Folder 9 - 13)
        [Currently removed for conservation treatment]
      - LRB&M Company Meetings - Oversized. Name indexes enclosed., Seaview Country Club, [NY]., 1952 - 1954, 6 (b&w prints) (Box Map Case 14-10-5, Folder 1 - 3)
      - Auerbach, Norman; Bardes, Philip; Bertine, Dorothy; Boedecker, Myron J; Breslin, Fred M; Burke, J. Edward; Campbell, Hilton R; Carson, Edward G; Case, Harry N; Friedman, Eugene; Giles, Claude R; Goldman, Ferne; Hawes, Hnery C; Henry, R[...]; Harvey, Joel D; Hunter, Albert E; Jennings, Alvin; Mahon, James J., Jr; Moore, Nickolas; Noell, Edwin P; Petty, Glen O.; Potter, John C.; Schweitzer, Gustave F.; Staub, Edmund A.; Staub, Walter; Steinmeyer, Harry H.; Walker, Mark C.; Zipf, Carl H.; Portraits of prominent employees (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Auerbach, Norman; Stewart, Clifford C&L Partners and wives, 1 (5 x 7 color print), 1 (6 x 8 color print) (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Hobart, Lawrence, C. Scovell, Wellington & Company Group photo with some name identifications., [Cleveland, OH], Sep. 30, 1962, 1 (3 x 4 color print) (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Training Programs: Elementary, Advanced and Senior Course -prints. Photos, sent by partner Victor Coppola (25 years club) Identifications enclosed., Philadelphia, PA, 17 (5x7 b&w print) (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - Training Programs: Elementary, Advanced and Senior Course -negatives. Photos, sent by partner Victor Coppola (25 years club) Identifications enclosed., Philadelphia, PA, 17 (3 x 3.5 b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - [Group of executives at lounge with flowers], [1994], 1 (8 x 10 color print), 1 (8 x 10 color transparency) (Box 30, Folder 26)
        [see also slides and Flat Box 1, Folder 2]
      - [Group of executives at lounge with flowers] - oversized print, 3 (12 x 14 color print) (Box 347, Folder 2)
      - Friedman, Eugene [Group of Executives]; Friedman with [Bronton Gough] prints, 6 (10 x 12 color print), 2 (contact sheets) (Box 347, Folder 3)
      - [Group of Executives]; Friedman with [Bronton Gough] negatives, 1990s, 20 (2.5 x 3 color negatives) (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous prints of unidentified company executives, 1990s, 8 (8 x 10 color print) (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - Distinguished partner Awards photos, 1994 - 1996, 8 (5 x 7 color print) (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - Retired Partners Luncheon. Name identification., New York, NY, 1997, 1 (8 x 10 color print) (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - Moore, Nicholas G.; Schiro, James J. PriceWaterhouseCoopers Merger with Price Waterhouse, 1998, 2 (5 x 7 b&w print) (Box 30, Folder 31)
      - unidentified transparencies and negatives: early 20th century ad; playing cards., 1 (4 x 5 color transparency), 2 (4 x 5 b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 32)
      - Three Eras of Lybrand, Dec. 1, 1969, 1 (35 mm color negatives(?) roll) (Box 30)
  - Subseries III.2: B&W Negatives Collection
    Negatives circa 1960s - 1970s, mostly undated. Collection contains some slide shows in both 35 mm and 4 x 5 formats.
    - Sub-subseries III.2.1: 35 mm negative strips
      Events, and workshops, partners and employees, slide shows (statistical and computer training).
      - 684 - Workshop, 72 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - 776-1 - [unid. Man], 8 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - 776-2 - Slide show: Statistical Sampling;Accelerated Data Manipulation through the use of Computer, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - 776-3 - Slide show: Basic Replenishment Planning Methods, 11 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - 846 - Slide show: Statistical Sampling, 23 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - 923-1 - Job Workshop, Barnes, Cordova & Eley Ltd. - L[ybrand] J[ournal], 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - 987-1, 987-4 - [unid. Cityscapes and office interiors}, 38 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - 987-5, 987-8, 987-9 - unid. Group of people, 92 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - 1115 - Slide show: Performance Measurement, reporting, 29 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - 1189-1 - Slide show: US Industrial outlook analysis, [1963], 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - 1189-2 - Slide show: GNP Forecasts, [1963], 12 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - 1194 - FEI-B, 8 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - 1242 - [Students in classroom], 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - 1403 - unid. Group of people, 35 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - 1518 - Slide show: [Using Computer, computer history and principles], [1965], 88 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - 1647 - unid. Group of people, 23 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - 1648 - Cartoon: First of all, Kaufman, I can't remember when I enjoyed a presentation more, 14 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - 1728 - [Students in classroom], 4 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - 1821 - Flash Test EDP (electronic data processing) General. Slide Show: [Third Generation Computers], 64 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - 1821-3 - [unid. Women in office], 14 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - 2446 - Slide Show: Trends, Multiple Time Series, Regression and correlation, 18 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - 2441 - [Classroom], 24 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - 2614 - Slide Show: [EDP and Auditing], 109 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - 2615 - Travelling Salesman Problem, 24 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - 2821 - Industry Meeting, Nov. 1967, 37 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - 2825 - Slide Show: computers. [Information flow and handling, Binary code, error sources, I/O devices, IBM 1050 Configuration, modes of data transmission, communication code characteristics, Methods of phone dialing, computer communications interface], 216 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - 2837 - Phone Operators, 10 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - 2839 - Slide Show: [Teletype], teletype operators, 28 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - 2875 - Industry Research Negatives., Apr. 24, 1968, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - 3001 - Partners Picture Book, 14 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - 3002 - [unidentified partner], 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - 3007 - Laguzza, 12 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - 3013-1 - [Event at Windsor Terrace], 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - 3013-2, 3013-3 - [unidentified event], 44 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - 3013-4 - [unidentified group watching slide presentation], 8 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - 3015 - [Women at unidentified even], 1960s, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - 3025 - Training Program, 1967, 81 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - 3029 - Journal Cover. [Classroom], 109 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - 3033 - [Classroom, inidentified people, refreshments], 72 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 38)
      - 3037-1 - Slide Show: [Work Fragmentation], 4 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 38)
      - 3037-2, 3037-3 - Slide Show: [Computer reporting and analysis system], 56 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 38)
      - 3039 - Contracts for O'Donnell [Slide show: Computer Data Processing], 9 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 38)
      - 3045 - Drew [university Training Program - classroom, cafeteria, landscapes], 132 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 38)
      - 3055 - Lang. [Slide Show: Computer and Information Flow], 133 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 39)
      - 3059 - L[ybrand] J[ournal] - Training Program, 112 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 39)
        [(see also 4x5 negs, same no.)]
      - 3061 - L[ybrand] J[ournal] - MEL - Black, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 39)
      - 3068 - [unidentified event], 57 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 39)
      - 3070 - RFM Mast - [Home Insurance], 28 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 39)
      - 3074 - NorthEast Region Managers Meeting. Lybrand Journal, Vol. 49, No. 2, 1968, 65 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 40)
      - 3086-2 - [2 unidentified women, unidentified man], 23 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 40)
      - 3088 - (see also 4x5 negs, same no.), 16 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 40)
      - 3090 - [Event at Mariott Motor Hotel], 131 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 40)
      - 3101 - Lybrand [computer], 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - 3441 - [IBM Computer vs. file cabinet, slide ruler etc.], 42 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - 3485 - Philadelphia Meeting. Norman Auerbach, 185 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - 3587 - [Slide ruler - Work Measurement], 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - 4009 - unidentified man; inidentified woman, 15 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - 4068 - Vanderpoe [Meeting], 8 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - 4072 - Henry Bedson - [Dinner], 35 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - 4076-1 - Slide Show: [Work Fragmentation, Computer and Work Simplification, Work Sampling and Analysis, Redundancy], 90 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - 4377 - Uncertain Designs [analysis], 25 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - 4410 - [IBM Computer vs. file cabinet, slide ruler etc.], 28 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - 4609 - Batzer, Pierce, 14 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - 4738 - Slide Show: [evaluation of inventory levels], 16 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - 5174 - American Client Meeting, Americana, New York, NY, 1966, 79 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - 5393 - American Client Meeting, Americana, New York, NY, 1966, 28 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - 5508 - [Classroom], 16 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - 5739 - L[ybrand] J[ournal] - Schnieder and Crest, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - 5742 - American Client Meeting, 35 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - 5974 - Partners Meeting, 1966, 165 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 43)
      - 6242 - [Classroom], 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 43)
      - 6503 - [Preparing Exhibit], 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 43)
      - 6606 - Printers Institute of America, 18 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 43)
      - 7022 - Computers: [slide ruler vs. keyboard, stuffing mail into envelopes], 72 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - 7033 - [Loading tape reel into IBM Mainframe Computer], 17 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - 7110 - [Exhibit - Project Structure], 16 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - 7143 - Slide show: [orientation and training - slide ruler, calendar, charts, work measurement and simplification], 72 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - 7485-1 - Slide show: [Management Reporting], 28 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - 7596 - Ken Johnson, [unidentified woman], 14 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - 7882 - Partners Meeting, 1966, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - 7911 - [Meeting], 40 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - 8107 - [Classroom, outdoor scenes], 139 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 45)
      - 8170 - [Classroom], 108 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 45)
      - 8365 - Ramsey, Gordon, 18 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 45)
      - 8528 - Warner & Co. for L[ybrand] J[ournal], 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 45)
      - 8566 - Warner & Co., Heiser, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - 8650 - [unidentified man and woman filing, answering phone], 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - 8741 - [unidentified man, unidentified woman], 22 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - 8948 - [unidentified man, unidentified woman], 22 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - 9013 - General Refactories Co. [Slide show - Feasibility Study], 25 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - 9277 - [Classroom], 118 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - 9292 - [Classroom], 47 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - 9369 - Hall, Lewis, 17 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - 9620-1 - P[ersonnel] D[ept.]. Graphic's Personnel Photos, 1968, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - 9620-2 - Eli Weinberg, Bache Brockerage Off[ice] Photos, 16 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - 10380 - Training Program, 1968, 24 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - 10408 - Advanced Audit Course, 1968, 56 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - 10417 - L[ybrand] J[ournal] - Computer Disks, 18 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - 10565 - Hospital Seminar, 12 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - 30035 - Advanced Audit Course, July [1968], 22 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - 30037 - Advanced Audit Course, 32 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - 31481 - Computers Installed on 50 Broad Street, Jul. 29, 1968, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - 31774 - Miss Rita Manning, 20 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - 31815 - Mr. John Laguzza, L[ybrand] J[ournal], Aug. 1968, 44 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - 31855 - Sampson, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - 31904 - Computer, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - 32280 - Stu Singer and group, 57 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - 32308 - Hospital Seminar at Broadway, 96 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - 32341 - Mrs. Rita Manning, Aug. 1968, 27 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - 32591 - Slide Show [Charts of computer memory and I/O devices], 40 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - 33919 - Weiss, 23 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - 34868- Debbie's Shower, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - 36016 - Warren Wintrub, 33 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - 36390 - Walter Staub, P. Defliese - executive Committee, 40 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - 36446 - Martin Dunleavy - candid photos, 1973, 5 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - 36520-1 - Computer Cutting Ceremony, Board Meeting (shot by Walter), Tax Advisory Committee, 1968, 76 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - 37076 - Philip Defliese, 32 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - 61687 - New CPA's, 1965, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - 64108 - [Classroom], 10 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - 70753 - O'Donnell and P.D. Dept., 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - 71451 - Mr. Henry, 22 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - 71469 - J. J. Mahon Lybrand Periodicals, 60 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - 72633-1 - Computers, 12 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 51)
      - 73826 - Defliese and 2 Medal Winners, P. D. 69, [1969], 60 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 51)
      - 74765 - L[ybrand] J[ournal] - Construction, [1969], 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 51)
      - 74861 - Staub-Retirement Photos for L. J., 1969, 72 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 51)
      - 74898 - [Lybrand Journal - Construction], 1969, 36 (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 30, Folder 51)